[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            1
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the unsupervised learning technique explored in this notebook?",
         "answer": "matrix factorization",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
         "cell_ids": [
           2
        ],
         "question": "What are the two main types of collaborative filtering mentioned?",
        "answer": "User-based and Item-based",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
   },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            2
        ],
        "question": "What is the purpose of the utility matrix in a recommendation system?",
         "answer": "The goal of our recommendation system is to build an mxn matrix (called the utility matrix) which consists of the rating (or preference) for each user-item pair.",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            2
         ],
        "question": "What do the U and V matrices represent in matrix factorization?",
         "answer":"U is a representation of users in some low dimensional space, and V is a representation of items.",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
       "cell_ids": [
            2
        ],
       "question": "What is the cost function that needs to minimized?",
       "answer":"Mean squared error",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
       "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
            11
        ],
       "question": "What is a common name for the type of recommendation system discussed in part I?",
       "answer": "Product popularity based system",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            11
        ],
        "question":"What is the criteria used for determining the rating of a user to an item in a collaborative filtering system?",
        "answer": "If a person rates a book more than his/her average rating then he/she likes the book.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
           14
        ],
         "question": "What is the name of the algorithm that is used for dimension reduction?",
        "answer": "PCA",
       "task": "Principal Component Analysis",
        "skill": "Kernel PCA"
    },
  {
      "cell_ids": [
          80, 82
      ],
      "question": "What range of years for book publication is used in the analysis after cleaning?",
        "answer":"1950 and 2016",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
           92
        ],
         "question": "What is the  maximum year of publication in Books dataset (before cleaning)?",
          "answer": "2050.000000",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    }
]